What's up everyone it's part of pulling the lever to continue talk
Talk about putting yourself out there
Last episode we talked about social media and online presence in general this month we're taking a closer look at interpersonal relationships in this
Industry and I'm also going to tell you the second mindset
The change my dating life forever
People in artist especially
Crossing reluctant to change their MO
They think that any kind of marketing is automatically manipulation
It often takes an enormous amount of convincing and motivating to get someone to even start presenting themselves online
And then there's this phrase I hear all the time
I just want to be
Myself
Well let's go back to dating
Because that's where I learned to be very careful with that phrase
It's easy to dismiss a bad conversation with a girl by saying
Well I was just being myself if she didn't like that that's her problem
This went on for a couple of years until I finally started to question this phrase
Was I really being myself
Or was I a stuttering nervous boring trihard version of myself
Unfortunately for a lot of people being yourself
Means being a kind of s*** version of themselves
For them being yourself means
I shouldn't put any work until I come across to others
Fortunately it is actually really easy to work on your confidence
One of my favorite quotes is leave with your mind and your body will follow
Speak with your body and your mind will follow
Is it scientifically proven connection between our body language and our thoughts
When you're happy
You smile
But it also works the other way around
When you smile
To get happy
It's the same with confidence
What kind of plane confidence
And you will feel
More confident
Now quick side note confidence does not mean being a dick
It means believing in yourself
Standing up for your decisions when I consider being a grown up
If you have low self-esteem I recommend you lead with your body
Work on confidence
Body language
Stand up straight
Move slowly
Talk slower and lower your pitch
Smile or laugh when it is appropriate
Not every time you're nervous
Don't fiddle around
Take your time
Q trip
Just get up
If you drop something
Pick it up
If you walk into the wrong direction
Just turn around
There's no need to tell everyone that you're an idiot in that stuff like that always happens to you
Talking to yourself like that is not helping
Everyone drops things
Everyone stumbles
Just ignore it
And others will too
Study the body language of powerful characters like James Bond or Rick Grimes and use it yourself
Sooner or later
Information that you're exhibiting confidence will reach your brain and at this point
Things got a lot easier
Dallas will feel strange at first
It's asking for a lot of self-control and you will overshoot in the beginning
But if you do this long enough you'll also find a balance that feels good
To you
No one is asking you to become colder shallow or superficial
This is all about increasing your awareness of how you come across as a person
She will truly be able to be
Yourself